So this is just a little pre-show chit-chat, okay?
I'm sewing up these pants.
My homegirl, she did the first layer of stitching, but I just wanted to reinforce it a little more.
So what's about to happen tonight is I'm about to do...
Oh, wow! Thank you, Busybody!
I'm about to do the live stream of What Would the Ancestors Say?
And I just want to remind y'all that it's live, okay?
There ain't no edits, all right?
There ain't no cutaways, okay?
This is real. This is theater.
So shout out to all of my...
I love how you're acting like it's weird that I'm in a bra when y'all see me in a bikini all the time.
All the time.
And so I just want to remind folks of that.
Okay?
Because this shit right here is real.
And we do have a discount code that will pop up during the live stream.
So anybody who's got their live stream tickets, you're going to get a discount.
So shout out to you.
All right?
So if you are still trying to see What Would the Ancestors Say?
You can go to AmandaSeals.com.
And if you're running late, you can still go to AmandaSeals.com.
Because we have tickets that are available for if you're running late.
And you'll still be able to watch whatever you missed for the next 72 hours.
Okay?
Hold on.
Let me block this.
This person.
Nope.
Don't bring none of that my way right now.
Don't bring none of that Trump shit.
I purposely have not looked at any of the news or nothing.
So keep that shit over there.
We're up here.
We're in high vibration space.
And we are about to go and do a show.
All right?
So you all appreciate all the love.
Go and get your copies.
Excuse me.
Of What Would the Ancestors Say?
It is available at AmandaSeals.com.
You can go to AmandaLandExports.com.
You can go to HelloAncestors.com.
All three of them are going to get you to the book.
Shout out to all of my creatives.
Shout out to all of my independent creatives.
Who make it happen.
Who figure it out.
And who have the support of others.
Who help them make it happen.
And figure it out.
Because I wouldn't be able to do the stuff I do without the folks that support me.
And that includes y'all.
See you soon.